{"response_code":0,"results":[{"category":"Science%3A%20Computers","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Linus%20Torvalds%20created%20Linux%20and%20Git.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Science%3A%20Computers","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The%20programming%20language%20%22Python%22%20is%20based%20off%20a%20modified%20version%20of%20%22JavaScript%22.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Science%3A%20Computers","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The%20logo%20for%20Snapchat%20is%20a%20Bell.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Science%3A%20Computers","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Ada%20Lovelace%20is%20often%20considered%20the%20first%20computer%20programmer.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Science%3A%20Computers","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"%22HTML%22%20stands%20for%20Hypertext%20Markup%20Language.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Science%3A%20Computers","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Time%20on%20Computers%20is%20measured%20via%20the%20EPOX%20System.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Science%3A%20Computers","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The%20Windows%207%20operating%20system%20has%20six%20main%20editions.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Science%3A%20Computers","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The%20Windows%20ME%20operating%20system%20was%20released%20in%20the%20year%202000.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Science%3A%20Computers","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The%20NVidia%20GTX%201080%20gets%20its%20name%20because%20it%20can%20only%20render%20at%20a%201920x1080%20screen%20resolution.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Science%3A%20Computers","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Linux%20was%20first%20created%20as%20an%20alternative%20to%20Windows%20XP.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]}]}